

#### CONTACT DETAILS

😲 3100 Sankt Pölten, Austria

+43 67763161304

bedo.faruk13@gmail.com

https://github.com/bedofares

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/abdelrahman-fares

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

#### Professional level in:

- HTML, CSS
- JavaScript
- JQuery
- UX / UI (Figma)

#### **Know-how in:**

- VueJs
- NodeJs
- Bootstrap / TailwindCSS
- DataBase: MySQL / SQLITE
- Android development (kotlin)
- Git

#### Fundamentals in:

- C#
- PHP, Laravel
- Python ML

# LANGUAGES

Arabic - native

English - C1

German - B1

# SOFT SKILLS

- Initiative and creativity
- Preciseness & attention to details
- Stress-resistance
- Excellent team worker
- Great communication
- Problem solving
- Problem sensitvity
- Punctual

# ABDELRAHMAN FARES

## JUNIOR FRONT END DEVELOPER

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a 20 years old Junior Front-end developer. I am currently in my second year of university, the fourth semester. I am seeking an opportunity to extend my web development skills and knowledge to grow as a professional. I am a supportive and enthusiastic team player dedicated to efficiently resolving project issues. I have the ability and willingness to innovate and learn new technologies, quick learner passionate about development.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Computer Science Co-Instructor

Diamond Coding academy, Cairo | Sep 2018 - Sep 2020

- Instructed more than 50 students in 3 different schools.
- 85% of the students got an A\* in this subject.
- Teached: HTML, CSS, JS Fundemntals.

#### Front-end developer

Ict Team, Cairo | Sep 2020 - Feb 2021

- 2 successfully closed projects.
- Used best practice in HTML and CSS to develop a static site based from a static image of a web design.
- Learned various technologies, developed preciseness and attention to detail.
- Excellently met the requirements of the projects over the whole work period.

## **EDUCATION**

## FH Sankt Pölten, Austria

BSc Creative Computing | Sep 2020 - July 2023

Majors: Web Technologies, User Interface Design, Mobile Programming, Game Design, and Augmented & Virtual Reality.

- Overall score 1.36
- Tuition Fee Waiver Scholarship for academic success in WS2020 & SS2021

## FH Wels, Upper Austria

Foundation degree for electrical engineering | Sep 2019 - July 2020

# Noor British International School

High school (IGCSE) | Sep 2017 - July 2019